Visit our website for more: turkision.com
No living being was harmed
during the filming of this series.
Allah is the Greatest!
Stay away from the windows!
There are archers everywhere!
They surrounded this side too, Malhun Hatun.
Everything is on fire!
What are we going to do?
Brother, we won't be able to get out
of the windows, they are everywhere!
Then we will get out of the door!
In the name of Allah!
Come on, Alaaddin.
Come on, Alaeddin, let's find
our mother!
We will get out, my daughter.
We will get out.
In the name of Allah!
Alaaddin.
My son.
Come, my girl.
Come on, son!
Son!
Come on.
Alaaddin, open the door!
Alaaddin, with shields!
In the name of Allah!
Mother!
Are you okay?
We are fine.
How is my sister?
We are fine, the Hatuns
are at the diwan, they need help.
Come on, sons, go!
I will make you regret coming to my
house and trying to harm my children!
Alps! Put out the fire!
Come on, Hüseyin.
We will see who is stronger now!
Come on.
Come on, Alps, we are
going to support Osman Bey.
Alaaddin!
Hatuns! Are you there?
Bayindir?
Bayindir, come on.
Step back, I will break the door.
The infidels are everywhere, they
want to burn down the palace.
But we will get out of
here, Inshallah, come on.
Come on.
Damned infidels!
Come on, hatuns!
Come on.
This is the battlefield, Osman Bey.
But, you need to go to Yenişehir.
There isn't anyone to protect them there.
I won’t leave you alone here.
Don't worry about here.
I have it under control.
Turgut.
Osman Bey, if Yenişehir falls, this
battle we have here won't mean anything.
Come on, Osman Bey.
Come on.
You're right.
If the palace fall,
our honor will fall with it.
Alps.
We're going to Yenişehir.
Come on.
Thank you.
Come on, we won't stop
until we reach Yenişehir. Come on.
Come on.
Don't let them run away from here!
Bala.
Did they go?
Kill them!
No one will leave this place alive.
Bala.
Halime.
Mother, are you okay?
Mother.
Aunt!
Bala.
Protect Bala.
Aunt!
Are you okay, mother?
Bala.
Esma.
Alaaddin.
Orhan.
Are you okay?
- We're okay.
You walk towards the fire, huh?
Come here.
Come.
You will burn!
You will burn alive.
Look at me.
Get up.
Get. Up.
Kneel.
You attacked my home...
my Hatuns and kids, huh?
Did you think you were going to
make it out alive?
This is your end.
Malhun.
Malhun..
Osman.
Are you okay?
I am okay.
My sons...
Orhan, Alaaddin..
We're fine.
Osman...
Halime and Bala...
Go!
Move!
Traitor...
Osman!
Bayındır helped us.
I will deal with you later.
Alps, put the fire out!
Come on.
My sons.
Let's go.
- Let's go!
- Hurry up!
Move!
Ya Shafi!
Give me my bag, Ülgen!
We have to make an ointment.
Bring it!
Ülgen!
We will cauterize the wound.
Tell the Alps...
...to bring embers.
Dark midwife.
Her arm is wounded too.
Put pressure on it.
Dogs...
Not even an
enemy would do this.
They tried to burn us here alive
because they are afraid to face us.
Bala...
Bala!
Bala.
Are you okay, Bala?
Bala...
Dark midwife, tell me...
She's okay.
She will be fine, my Bey.
She's a mother...
and mothers are strong.
They protect their children
with their lives.
They're strong!
Don't you worry.
Are you hurt, my Bey?
I'm fine.
Bala..
Halime...
Halime!
Bala!
What is this?
Halime is fine, Osman Bey.
Alçiçek is making her sleep.
She's alright.
Tell me what happened.
I want to know everything.
My child...
You're going to be fine.
Osman ran away...
but I have you, Turgut.
I will separate your skin...
from your bones.
You're mistaken, Nayman.
My people don't run away.
He’ll show up...
in such an unexpected time that...
you won't see him coming here.
I will kill everyone...
who are against me.
It’s your turn now, Turgut.
We live for martyrdom.
I can die gladly.
However, the ones after us...
will spread the words of Allah, Inshallah.
Do whatever you're going to do!
What are you waiting for?
Come on!
Look...
Take a good look...
Brother...
My Bey.
Kutan.
It was an honor for me to walk this
road with you, Turgut Bey.
Will you give me your blessing?
Kutan.
Will you, my Bey?
My Bey?
Of course, brother, I give
you my blessing.
I bear witness that there
is no deity but Allah...
Don't do it, kill me instead of him!
Kutan.
Nayman.
Acar...
The soldiers of Islam die once
but we will be reborn as thousands!
You will lose your head, too, Nayman!
My Bey, will you give me your blessing?
I give you my blessing, brother.
I bear witness that there
is no deity but Allah...
and I bear witness that Muhammed is
His servant and messenger.
Nayman!
Even if you go to hell..
I will come and find you!
Malhun!
Prepare all of the Alps.
Yenişehir will become a
powerful place.
Put archers on top
of the walls and towers.
No one will move
without my knowledge.
Boran.
My Bey.
Prepare the soldiers.
We will go help Turgut Bey.
Your command, my Bey.
Cerkutay.
My Bey.
You will learn how many horsemen
and infantry they have.
Your command, my Bey.
Baysungur.
My Bey.
You will call everyone in the surrounding
tribes to Söğüt and Yenişehir.
Your command, my Bey.
Gürbüz.
My Bey.
You will go to Nayman's headquarters.
You will learn who goes there.
Your command, my Bey.
Osman.
What about Bayindir?
What are we going to do with him?
If he wasn't here, things would be worse.
I will deal with him.
Malhun.
The children and Yenişehir
are in your care.
I will go to the headquarters
with Boran.
Don't worry.
Turgut Bey...
Osman Bey!
How did they escape?
What were you doing, Celali?
Mother Sultan, as soon as Osman
learned about Yenişehir...
he returned to the palace.
Otherwise, it was impossible for Hatuns to survive.
Bayındır.
Where is he?
If Osman captures him...
he will learn everything.
That I worked with Nayman.
There is no news...
from Bayindir and Hüseyin, Mother Sultan.
They couldn't do the job!
Fools!
No!
It's not okay to stay here now.
Prepare the horses, we are leaving.
My Bey.
I have Turgut.
I give you 15 days.
Your Alps and people will
drop their weapons.
If you make any move, I will
kill Turgut and, then your people.
If you go under my rule, you can live.
I will never give my people to you...
or give Turgut to you.
You have a seal and you have so many
cruel men behind you.
I swear...
I'm going to make
these lands your grave.
I swear!
2 weeks later
It's time, huh, Osman?
You're right, Bala.
It’s time.
We've been waiting for
this day for a long time.
May it be Mubarak. (holy)
But..
Tell me.
Is it the right time?
A tree that doesn't root
during hard times...
would crumble with a breeze of wind.
We'll try now, Bala.
May Allah help you.
Amin.
Amin, Inshallah.
Come on.
These need one more emery.
Mother.
Come and take a look.
Do it one more time.
Carefully.
We'll prepare it
right away, Malhun Hatun.
You're tired.
You don't ever sleep but it will be
worth your efforts, Inshallah.
Inshallah.
Mashallah.
Beat it, valiants, beat it.
Beat it.
Beat it like you're beating infidels!
Beat it for your late master.
A martyr's blood...
and a craftsman's sweat.
If those two are there, a piece of
land becomes a nation.
We went through a lot.
We will go through more but...
we won't stop!
It was waiting for the right
time and now it is.
It is.
It is, brother.
Okay. This is good.
Thank you for your work.
Come on, move the tables to the square.
Good work.
Hadrat Sultan...
there's a letter from Osman Bey.
Hand it over, Vizier.
Let's see what Osman Bey
wants from us.
Hadrat Sultan...
I’m going into battle for defeating the
Mongols who once were in your palace.
That's why I...
would wish to see the
soldiers you once promised.
Osman Bey...
is asking for the soldiers
I've promised to him.
My Sultan.
Excuse me...
but my opinion is...
that Nayman has the seal...
and that makes me doubt if we should
be his enemy.
Since when..
do you question the Sultan's orders?
Clerk.
Write this.
May Osman Bey's sword be sharp
and his fight be victorious.
The army he wishes for...
will be given to him.
Vizier.
You can leave.
I'm going to talk to Sultan...
alone.
Everyone leave.
When a lot of traitors
have roamed this palace...
do you think I would give you a
Vizier who is not loyal to me?
You won't make any moves
against Nayman.
Because..
I've given the seal to him.
Let's see...
In the name of Allah, the most
gracious and the most merciful.
Well...
Now...
My Sheikh.
In the name of Allah, the most
gracious and the most merciful
Oh, Allah!
My Sheikh.
Let me see...
Mashallah...
The sizes are pretty similar.
InshaIIah...
when these are done...
then...
we will pay all merchants
with this silver coin.
We will use these to pay
for all caravans.
Blacksmiths...
you have a crucial task
ahead of you.
Start making these at once.
Your command, my Bey.
But..
look at the sides.
I want you to...
fix them as well.
Your command, my Bey.
40 of these..
will let you gather a caravan.
40 of them will pay for 50 swords.
Nayman gave us 15 days to surrender.
So before that time runs out..
we will do what needs to
be done for our freedom.
Inshallah.
May Allah keep you
in His path, Osman Bey.
You're planning to
do a good deed.
May it end well for all of you.
Inshallah, my Sheikh.
InshalIah.
Once the coins are all done..
we will use them
to pay for all our trades.
That way, it will spread even faster.
Inshallah, our coins will be used
to trade all over these lands.
Inshallah.
Inshallah, my Sheihh.
Inshallah, my Sheikh.
Kumral Abdal.
Gather iron, silver and copper...
Sort them all out..
and prepare them to be forged.
Get it done by tomorrow.
Inshallah, we will see this
done Osman Bey...
but how are we going to hit Nayman?
Sultan Alaaddin promised to
send us an army.
The army will encourage
the Beys to stand by our side.
Let’s wait until the army is here.
If your intention is to hit
Nayman, Osman Bey...
all Alps of our tribe will follow you.
Isn't that right, Aktemur Bey?
Yes!
Your command, my Bey.
Thank you...
but there's a time for everything.
We have something
else to deal with for now.
My Sheikh...
let's make our sacrifices.
Nayman.
Oh souls, salute Nayman!
Oh souls, salute Nayman.
Nayman, the greatest!
The souls are greeting the greatest
Nayman, sir.
Nayman, the greatest!
I made the night sleep 15 times!
I made the sun go mad 15 times!
For what?
For today!
Where are the Beys?
They are on their ways, Nayman.
They will be here for the council.
Those who can't make it in time...
will die.
They will either stand with me...
or they will die!
Kutan.
Acar.
You can rest easy.
I am going to kill all of
them with my hands.
Then I will meet you.
You can rest easy.
What's the situation
in Yenişehir, tell me.
The construction for the soup
kitchen began, my Bey.
Until aunt Bala's wounds heal, Alçiçek
will take care of the soup kitchen.
Many people come and ask for
our help every day. Thank Allah.
This soup kitchen is important.
Alçiçek took responsibility in my absence.
But my wounds are healed now, I
will return back to the work quickly.
Alçiçek must be tired.
No.
A blessed duty like this
wouldn't tire any of us.
No.
The people matters more.
That's why, Alçiçek will stay at the
soup kitchen for a little longer.
Bala.
You have another duty.
Yes, my Bey.
They are surrounding us from all sides.
We will not wait here or outside.
We will always walk forward.
What about Turgut Bey?
Nayman thinks that we
will stop because he has Turgut.
And until the time he has given us comes...
he won't do anything.
We will save Turgut.
Now tell me.
How are the preparations in Yenişehir?
We took precautions in Yenişehir, Osman Bey.
But the enemy is still inside.
What are we going to do against İsmihan?
The real question is what will Ismihan do.
What if he stops the
army that will come here?
We know İsmihan is in Konya now.
As long as Sultan Alaaddin
sits on the throne...
we can't do anything.
Maybe that's what she wants.
They still have time.
How could you do that, mother?
How could you give the seal to him?
Aren't you worried about
the future of our land?
I gave it because I care about it!
Is this how you care?
By giving unlimited power to Nayman?
There is no other option
to get rid of Osman
I can't understand.
I can't understand it! We are
on the same side with Osman.
How can we be on the same side as
a rebellious Bey who wants to be free?
Nayman is an enemy!
But Osman is a traitor, Alaaddin.
When Nayrnan...
removes Osman from these lands...
he will leave.
He will give Konya and the borders to us.
That's what'we agreed on.
Mother.
How can you trust a Mongolian?
I don't trust anyone.
Nayman is going to destroy
Osman with that seal!
Then, he will go after Gazan.
As they're destroying each other,
we'll be the most powerful in these lands.
For our future, there
is no other way.
With the power of immortal God...
those who are destined
with the world dominance!
Let the council begin.
First, we will swear an oath.
Without swearing an oath,
there can't be a council.
Our blood will be mixed.
We will swear an oath.
It will be mixed.
And the blood will be drunk!
Our freedom...
is in Nayman's command.
Our sword..
is held by Nayman!
Our fate is in Nayman's hands!
Drinking this to destroy
those who stand against us!
Drinking...
this to move Cengiz's legacy further.
This legacy which goes
from China to Byzantine.
We won't leave it to
those who are in betrayal.
From Tebriz, Karakurum..
Hanbalık you have come from.
We swore and saw the seal.
Now...
our soldiers who
have been waiting can come.
Tendağ.
Send the messengers.
This world has been created by
the Sky Tengri (God) for the strong to rule.
There are small bugs...
like Osman.
We will end them for those who
might get the wrong idea.
Mongolian chanting
My Bey, there's word.
Thank you.
It's about the Beys who
went to Nayman's invitation.
They reached Nayman's
headquarters.
And they went there with
a lot of presents too.
Those are for Nayman.
They want to get close to him.
But..
But their army won't be with them.
Why is the reason, my Bey?
They want to decide about
the army during the council.
If the order is ruled...
then...
they will send messengers
to the commanders.
What they are intending is...
to see if the seal is real or not.
Who will be their commanders?
Nayman is after a
strong move right now.
Those commanders...
have the same blood as
the ones at the council.
Either their son...
or son in law...
or their niece.
Nayman is preparing a move that
will go on for years.
That's why...
he's collecting...
those who are the strongest
without caring for their ages.
But we won't..
let the messengers pass.
If they do...
if the army comes...
we can't get Turgut...
or stay free.
Your command, my bey.
May I come in, my Bey?
Come in.
My Bey.
There is a word from the Alps.
As you said...
he council sent the messengers away.
Everyone will go
to their posts.
Come on, Alps.
The armies will be here.
But there will be people
who will stand against you.
What will be your move
against them, Nayman?
When....
Cengiz Khan's seal is in my hands...
everyone who goes
against me is a traitor.
When the armies come..
I’m going to declare
myself as the Khan.
I'm going to make those who
got off the path get back on it.
I'm going to destroy those who...
try to stop us.
Who are those?
Muslims.
They tricked people.
The people of the nation...
are choosing Islam day by day.
The commanders in Konya
are choosing Islam.
They're disappearing.
Sky Tengri is leaving us
slowly because of them.
Under my Khanate...
not one of them will live.
We will be reborn
with your rule.
Shaman.
Throw the bones in the fire.
Let the fire show us...
who will come victorious out of this war.
It's either now..
or never, Cerkutay.
Cerkutay?
Are you hungry?
You need to wait a little.
There's no time to wait, Ülgen.
There's no time.
I will make you something else then.
It’s not that.
There's just no time.
Ülgen...
do you know what I first thought of...
when I saw the palace in fires?
What was it?
It was you.
I wondered where you were...
and how you were doing.
My heart was aching.
- Cerkutay...--
- Wait, Ülgen.
I've been meaning to say
these things for a long time...
so while I'm at it...
let me speak.
You know, I had buried my
heart under the dirt.
But you pulled it back out.
I'm in love with you, Ülgen.
Ülgen?
Ülgen...
Ülgen!
Oh no, it’s the dark midwife!
Where are you, Ülgen?
Ülgen!
Girl...
Girl!
Are you okay?
I'm in love with you, too.
What?
Get up!
You're in love, huh?
Mother?
Yes!
I must have fallen asleep.
Thousands of soldiers are waiting on
your command, Nayman the Great.
The Shaman pointed out
to a victory!
Why don't we destroy
Yenişehir right now?
Osman is making Yenişehir
a strong castle.
He's being very careful.
Do you think we'll lose more than
what we'll win?
I will not send the soldiers there
before the army arrives.
Once the army is here, not only
we'll destroy Yenişehir...
but we will also bring
chaos to all their lands!
Is it just Osman?
You're not easily satisfied...
are you?
The army will march on the Byzantines...
and destroy all other Beys as well.
Then, what?
We already know what we'll win...
Slaves, maidens...
and lots of spoils.
After the war...
we will march towards Tebriz and Gazhan!
Then...
we'll set out for the whole world!
The whole world!
Can I come in, Mother Sultan?
Come in, Bayındır.
Mother Sultan.
We've made all
preparations for the road.
We're ready.
Did you check twice, Bayindir?
You know...
you haven’t done anything right...
since your failure at the palace.
Mother Sultan...
hearing you speak like that
makes me wish that...
I was dead along with those soldiers.
- When Osman Bey came...--
- Shut up!
You're unskilled...
yet you're smart.
You know when to switch your side
once you realize it won't end well.
Mother Sultan...
you can trust your humble servant Bayindir.
I'm always on your side.
However...
about Nayman's council...
What do you mean, Bayindir?
Mother Sultan, I don't
trust that infidel...
Nayman.
I wonder...
if there is a trick behind this.
I will side with them.
Why are you mad, my Bey?
Did something happen?
From now on, I will side with the
ones that follow Allah's path.
Let's see if we can stop Ismihan before...
she reaches the council.
So, Mother Sultan plays a game, huh?
Are we going to make a
plan against them, my Bey?
So...
I don't trust you, Bayindir.
You should know that.
I would never trust you.
Now...
with your smallest mistake...
my sword will fall onto your neck.
I will sacrifice my
life for you, my Bey.
May Allah grant me martyrdom
while fighting for you.
I repented for my sins, my Bey.
From now on, I will not play any trick
against anyone that is not an infidel.
We will see.
We will live and see.
Now, you will go to Mother Sultan.
You will make her and
Nayman fight each other.
When they are weakened..
I will take care of the rest.
Come on.
My Bey, what was the reason
for that slap?
For what you have done!
Leave!
Your command, my Bey.
Send word to Osman Bey quickly.
İssmihan stopped the army that
was going to leave Konya.
We are returning to Söğüt now.
Come on.
Brother, they are coming.
I heard it, brother.
We will not let anyone pass.
Okay.
Stop, warriors!
Who can stop Nayman's messenger?
Well, not me, brother, it's Osman
Bey's orders.
It was a clean job, huh, brother?
Thank Allah.
What's written on it?
What's that brother?
To the horses.
Stop!
What do you want?
Stop there.
Where are you going?
Are you carrying a message from Nayman?
Nayman took precaution.
How did you understand, brother?
The letter the messenger was carrying
was empty. This is the real letter.
The route of the Beys from
the council is written on it.
Turahan, send word to Alps.
Tell them not to allow any
merchant carriages or villagers to leave.
Mother Sultan...
you thought so well.
If Sultan Alaaddin doesn't send an army..
Osman will have a hard time.
But...
when he learns that you've done this...
he will attack you with everything he has.
No.
Nayman has weakened Osman.
Osman doesn’t have the strength for
another fight.
He knows that he will
lose his head if he rebels.
The only thing he doesn't know is
that Nayman and I are on the same side.
And that will lead us to victory.
Betrayal to Seljuk won't
be looked over.
But...
can we trust Nayman, Mother Sultan?
A commander who wants to
rule over the world...
Why would he let you get stronger?
We have the same goal
with Nayman, Bayındır.
We agreed to destroy Osman.
He will stay loyal to it.
You know the best but we
still need to be careful.
Nayman feeds on blood.
When Osman falls, may Allah forbid...
he might turn towards you.
I decide on the target, Bayindir.
Both Osman and Nayman will be destroyed.
The ruler of these lands...
will be me.
Come on.
The relatives of the Mongol
Beys will come with a big army.
He wants them to come without resting.
Then...
we will make them our guests in a inn.
An army without its commander
can’t move.
We'll capture the relatives of the
Mongol Beys in the caravanserai.
I would let them go under one condition.
They will leave our lands.
The seal unites them.
But we will stop that.
They will get out of our lands.
If they don't give Turgut Bey
in exchange for them...
...I'm going to kill them
in front of their relatives.
My bey.
Change the compass.
Their commanders will enter
the in from Ingoz route.
As you wish my bey.
Now everyone goes back to their job.
Come on.
My bey.
My bey that's Mongol's military inn.
They won't believe it otherwise.
We will go to the inn beforehand...
...and take it.
And we are going to welcome them.
Tell me about the inn.
As you wish my Bey.
My Bey.
Come on.
Who are you?
I'm...
...Cerkut Tay.
And this is my slave.
You enslaved a Turk, huh?
Good job, good job.
Let me give you a tip, soldier.
A Turk can never be enslaved.
The commanders..
...are coming to our lands to spill blood.
Their armies are deployed in the valley.
Let them come.
Let them.
We will show them how hospitable we are.
We'll cook.
Alps.
Everyone go to their jobs!
As you wish my Bey!
Come on.
Let them come.
Let them.
Bala.
Let's go.
Welcome, royal commanders.
Welcome, mighty commanders.
Eat well.
Once Nayman and our ancestors start the war...
...we will have no time to eat or rest.
Keep eating.
We'll sip on Turk blood after our meals!
Who are you?
Don't you know no one is allowed here
while the commanders are coming?
Where are you going?
To the battle!
To make mountains out of Turks' bones.
To drink their blood!
Who's in the lead?
Someone called Osman Bey
You're looking at him.
Are you Osman?
I am.
We were looking for you, Osman.
Behold!
Stay put if you want him to keep his head!
Even hundreds of you...
...are still no match for Turgut only.
You may keep breathing until...
...the council is disbanded...
...and Turgut is back.
We were on our way to kill you but
you welcomed us on the way, Osman
You will die!
As long as our base is still there..
...you, your Alps...
...and that Hatun of yours-
You don't know anything about the land
you're going after...
This is the land of Muslims...
The land of Turks!
You may enter...
...however...
...you can't leave before you die.
Even if it takes centuries..
...we will make sure you acknowledge that.
Bring him!
You can leave.
You're here because you thought...
...you had what it takes to face me, Turgut.
But you lost.
You will witness the great state
I am about to found.
The dream you always have for...
...ruling the whole world...
...will be the end of the Mongols.
But your end...
...will be by the hand of my brother,
Osman Bey!
No one can stop me...
...as long as I have this seal.
I know the sea
I once possessed it
I took it by personally cutting your
brothers throat.
Was it Talay?
Talay...
Your efforts to get yourself killed...
...are in vain.
I killed your Alps, remember?
My army is on it's way.
I will make Inegol my stable
My stable!
We'll see...
..what fate has in store for us.
What now, Osman?
Alps...
...you, too, might be wondering...
...how we're going to go to
Nayman's council...
...with the Mongolian army
standing outside.
He who had a plan to get in...
...must have a way out as well, my Bey.
Of course I do.
-Cerkutay.
-My Bey.
Here..
...is a letter that says
the army isn't needed...
...and the forces are to
return to their posts.
Now...
...all commanders will put
their seals under it.
If they don't...
...we will kill them.
My Bey.
Do you think they will believe me?
They will.
Of course they wi
Do you see that one?
You will go there as his aide.
You will keep your dagger on his back.
He will give the letter to the army.
If he tries anything, cut his
head in front of the army.
As you command my Bey.
Give the letter and come back, Cerkutay.
Come on.
If you say something wrong...
...I will cut your throat before
you finish your sentence.
Come on.
Once the army is scattered...
...you're going to go to the secret
headquarters to get prepared.
We'll see how much the commanders
love their relatives.
We will make them go through every move
they intended to use on us.
What about Turgut Bey?
We'll take him too, don't worry.
Once the army is scattered...
We still have time for now.
Carvers will start to throw the coins
with the first sun rays in the morning.
We should have everything ready.
We don't have anything missing,
don't worry.
Go tell the Alps that...
...they will move the silvers here
from the mines at dawn.
As you command, mother.
As you command.
Our mission is important.
Everyone in Yenisehir is waiting for it.
For that reason, be careful.
We have a lot of friends but we
have more enemies.
May Allah help us.
Amen.
Tell me..
...Bengi Hatun.
What happened here in our absence?
You must have heard about
what happened, Mother Sultan.
You have eyes and ears everywhere.
But the information
I am going to give you is different.
What is it?
Osman.
He won't stop.
What he is doing now...
He is printing coins.
What do you mean he prints coins?
He can't dare to do that!
He did, Mother Sultan.
Malhun is taking care of that.
They are working hard.
They took care of everything.
Bad manners!
Do you know what this means, Bengi Hatun?
It means that he is not acknowledging
the Seljuk .state anymore!
This means that he is on his on now!
Osman manages to turn all kinds
of defeats beneficial for himself.
Now he is trying to win the favor of
immigrants of Yenisehir with a soup kitchen.
Yenisehir took many
migrations, Mother Sultan.
Osman is getting more powerful.
Osman!
He is still not aware of whom he is facing
We need to stop Osman.
Or it will be late.
He will -stop.
Osman will stop.
First, we will stop the printing
of the coins!
We will stop that.
Now listen to me refully, Bengi Hatu
Come on, we need to hurry. Malhun Hatun
asked us to return with daylight.
You did well, Aybars.
You were right.
This is where Malhun's iron is.
How are we going to move away the alps?
Should we kill them?
I thought something forthat. Don't worry.
Alps, come on.
We will stop them, come on.
Come with me.
Peace be with you, brothers.
Peace be upon you.
Who are you?
Malhun Hatun sent me.
She said 1 carriage wouldn't be enough,
so told us to bring the second carriage.
Okay, we will leave, so you can bring it.
She told us to bring her
the loaded carriage.
Then take the carriage,
we will follow you after filling this one.
Come on, safe travels.
Come on brothers.
Come on.
This will be so embarrassing
for you Osman.
This time no one can save you.
Come on Alps.
Change the baskets.
Won't they know these are damaged?
They won't.
Mother Sultan says..
...these...
...are worthy when they're melted.
They’re both the same.
But when this melts, it's trash.
But when this melts it's valuable.
Come on.
Hurry up! Come on!
Finish preparations Celali.
We'll leave.
Hadrath Mother Sultan...
Forgive me but...
...I don't feel good about this.
What if Nayman's playing a game?
You've been sayin the same thing.
How do you know this is a game of Nayman?
What's your point?
The rising sun of Great Seljuk.
This poor servant..
...only aims to save your life.
That's all.
However...
...I was with that infidel...
...long enough to get to know him.
If he wanted to trick us..
...he would have done it by now.
Bayindir.
But you should feel at ease.
I won't die today.
Today I will become the ruler of this land.
That's why we're going to the council.
But..
...if you have fear in your heart...
...stay.
Our path is a hard one.
Those who have fear in their hearts...
...can't walk Bayindir.
Your path is my own Mother Sultan.
That's all I know.
What's going on Osman?
Bala.
It's time to keep the promise I made you.
What promise?
I made a promise to you when
we were in that cruel's inn.
I'm going to keep it now.
What promise?
Don't you remember?
No I don't.
Remind me.
Okay then.
You'll remember when you see it.
Besides...
...let's see if your wounds are healed.
I'm okay.
I would beat you even in this state Osman Bey.
If you say so.
Yeltutan?
Come on son.
Are you ready?
Alacan did you hear what he said?
Come on dear.
Come on.
We're going to throw those to them who else?
Konur.
Brother.
You didn’t tell us about the inkwell issue.
Allah Allah.
He's right Konur.
You just change the subject.
Brothers.
He's keeping it a secret.
He always has some secrets.
Konur doesn't like to
talk about his accomplishments.
But you have no other option
but to tell us, Konur.
While you were fighting
at the headquarters...
...I was fighting for the ink pen.
I don't know what you're asking.
It's clear you went through a tough fight.
If it was Cerkutay he would've talked
about it nonstop for 15 days.
I win every fight I get into...
...and tell about it but...
..I'm in an undecided fight right now.
You'll see it all when I win anyways.
We called him lunatic for too long.
Do you think we might've
turned him into one?
After what great Nayman does to you...
...the ones who die will be lucky.
Those who are left alive
will all be lunatic.
Shut it.
Do you think you can take us to great
Nayman's headquarters...
...and get out of there alive?
All of you.
All of you will die.
Did you think that my Bey
was going to take you there?
You're the ones who will die.
My bey's order.
Take everything...
...with a mark on them.
Nayman and his beys...
...will see that we have the commanders
of their blood in our hands.
Stay put or I'll let Cerkutay deal
with you.
What are you looking at, Nayman's dog?
I'm talking to you!
Can’t you hear?
Are you only brave when you're crowded?
Aren't you even brave enough to answer
me on your own?
Nayman's little puppy.
Soldiers!
I will take all of you down for what
you've done to my Alps!
I will destroy you!
I will kill all of you...
...one by one!
Filthy Turk!
Let me go!
Let me go
He cut the ropes with this bone.
Where's my army?
Why aren't they here?
They should have been here .by now, but-
You're going to find out where my army is!
Don't you trust us at all, Nayman?
Don't worry, Nayman.
Nothing can stop that army.
They will be here soon.
No one can dare stand in.their way.
No one can..
...stop the army with swords...
However...
...they might be tricked.
Who could do such a thing.
Osman.
I have no problem defeating enemies...
...but I still can't figure out a way to
defeat my Hatun.
MashAllah.
Once again, I'm no match for you.
Indeed.
Alright...
Alright now...
Come here.
How nice is that?
MashAllah...
I couldn't even think of coming here
with everything that's going on.
Look at them.
Look how beautiful they are.
Bala, I promised you.
That I would bring you
to see these flowers.
Here you go.
We should keep our promises quickly.
We shouldn't wait on them.
Death is close to us like our breath.
That's right.
People think it's not close,
but you realize it when you almost die.
Being close to death does not scare us.
You just think about the ones
you leave behind.
Death is for all of us.
But separation, longing.
That's the hard part.
May Allah not test us with that,
InshAllah.
Amen, may Allah give you
a long life, my Bey.
Ameen.
But when I saw you among flames like that.
Bala, you, the children...
Being a father is harder than battles.
You were the winner of that
tough battle, Osman Bey.
Your children are brave
and strong like you.
My Bey.
We got word from our scouting alps.
They are on the move.
So it's time for the duty, huh?
Time for duty.
Did you prepare the equipment?
Here, Osman Bey.
Who is on the move?
What duty is this, Osman Bey?
Ismihan.
She stopped the army
I asked from Sultan Alaeddin.
Nayman invites her to the council.
If he takes the seal..
...then he would give her
the power she wanted.
And he would involve
Ismihan into the council.
What's in the bag?
Disguises that would make Ismihan
believe Nayman attacked him.
EyvAllah Osman Bey.
So we just did not come here
to pick flowers, huh?
No.
What are you waiting for?
Go and pick some flowers for Alcicek
As you command my Bey.
My Bala.
It's your duty now.
You will stop Ismihan
from entering the council.
Don't worry.
Pick them up faster.
Osman's time is up today.
He always has a plan.
The commanders of our
blood leads the army.
No one can stop our progress.
Great Nayman.
The army will come.
But tell us.
Who will replace Talay?
Whoever gives the seal to me.
Will you let a Turk step in?
Empires don't care about race.
Great Empires..
...are ruled with competence.
Ismihan deserves this position.
I'll give her that power.
She will rule the borders in my name.
Send Warriors to welcome Ismihan.
There will be no mistakes.
A Turk in the council?
That has never happened!
We'll do many more things
that never happened.
Many things.
You will obey.
And we'll praise Genghis.
But don't you worry.
He'll kill Turgut for us..
...and prove her loyalty.
Kan!
Let Turgut in.
Now.
Soldiers!
Attack!
Warriors.
We shouldn't have trusted Nayman,
Hadrat Mother Sultan.
There's too many. We must retreat.
I'll take my revenge.
Come on. Retreat!
Come on.
Protect Mother Sultan.
Run Ismihan run!
The only reason that arrow is
not in your heart...
...is Sultan Alaeddin's shadow.
When the time comes,
you won't run from our justice.
Thank Allah we're saved.
Mother Sultan'Hadrath.
We barely escaped. Barely
I told you. We shouldn't
have trusted Nayman.
Shat up Bayindir. Shut up
How could Nayman do this?
Mother Sultan Hadrath.
He wants to be the only ruler.
Nayman doesn't want to share power.
You wore alp clothes before.
And now warrior clothes.
I was wondering which clothes
I was going to be seeing you tomorrow.
You should look at yourself first.
I was thinking whatever
you wore suited you, but...
...turns out you are the one who make
the clothes look good, Alcicek Hatun.
My bey.
Alps will stand around the headquarters.
They will attack at the
smallest of the moves.
And the rest will tend to them.
As you wish my bey.
Konur.
Cerkutay.
Baysungur.
You'll keep your hands on your weapon.
If they aim a sword at Turgut Bey...
...you’ll end them.
We'll take Turgut Bey.
This will end today.
The end will come to those who...
...wish to spill blood
on these lands.
Come on.
Keep your eyes peeled.
No one should know we did this.
Aunt.
Why are we doing this?
No one would benefit from those coins.
Don't ask like you don't know.
Do whatever I
Don't question the rest niece.
To gain power...
...we need Mother Sultan.
We'll do whatever she says.
There's no other way.
Bengi Hatun.
Welcome.
Welcome to you too.
I came to bring the bags
Ayse Hatun send to Alcicek Hatun.
Good.
This is your tribe too.
I didn't ask you why you came right?
eave then.
I shouldn't be late.
Go on.
Why are they doing this?
This was Osman's last day to...
...leave...
...his weapons and swore his loyalty.
He didn't come.
And he will start to
pay for it with Turgut’s death.
Do you-see someone...
...who is not willing to do so?
I don't.
My armies are on the way.
I'm going to flood Osman's
lands with blood.
Those you don't obey
are destined to die Turgut.
Don't worry.
You're going to pay that price.
You always...
...talk about spilling
innocent people's blood.
Did you ever think about
how you'll pay for that?
You'll...
...pay for it...
...dying...
...painfully by our hands.
But...
...you will be killed by Ismihan.
I'm always going to
make you kill each other.
Who can take me to account?
Who knows?
Maybe I will.
Osman Bey is here!
Brother...
Osman is here.
Osman Bey...
Let's see...
Oh Allah, let us succeed...
In the name of Allah..
NAYMAN’S BASE
Osman!
Didn't you expect to see me?
Your sword is still in it's sheath.
I see that...
...you're hot here to surrender.
You've taken Turgut as a prisoner...
..and went against my home!
Boran.
Put those away!
Soldiers.
Here...
These are from the commanders
of the army that you're waiting for.
These, too.
I've captured your commanders...
...and the army you're waiting
for will not come.
My nephew
This belongs to my brother!
Stop him, Nayman!
Save our sons and nephews
Nayman-
Our families, Nayman....
Our brothers!
The soldiers you called to spill
blood on my home...
..have all gone back to their homes.
I sent them all away.
The life of your commanders
depend on my words.
Save them, Nayman.
Do something.
What do you want, Osman?
You will release Turgut...
...and the Beys will get their
commanders back.
Otherwise..
...even the seal won’t help you.
Nayman...
Mighty Naymaö
Stop him.
You're in deep waters.
You're just making the war bigger...
...instead of surrendering.
The price you'll pay will be great!
No...
The war was already big enough.
is a battle betwee right and wrong.
But I swear that..
...no matter how great...
...or how strong you are...
...the winner of this war...
...can only be us.
Now release Turgut!
Or the commanders will die.
The choice is yours.
They're our blood, Nayman.
Let Turgut go.
Soldiers!
I knew that you'd come, brother.
Thank you.
You might have won today...
..but I will be the one
who wins in the long run.
When we reach for our swords,
we always become the winner!
Visit our website for more: turkision.com